Switchmen's Union of North America Records 5034
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Switchmen's Union of North America Records
1834-1971
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Switchmen's Union of North America (SUNA)
5034
94.06 cubic feet
94.1 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Included in this collection are constitutions; by-laws, convention and Board of Director Minutes; officer's records; financial documents; strike, arbitration, wage and vacation files and a host of ancillary documents and photographs as well as oral history transcripts in which S.U.N.A. leaders discuss the merger with the U.T.U.
3338456
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, December 07, 2012
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 04, 2019
Biographical / Historical
The Switchmen's Union of North America is among the older of the railway brotherhoods. Beginning in 1877 with the formation of a local Switchmen's organization in Chicago, the movement became national when the Switchmen's Mutual Aid Association of North America held its first meeting nine years later.
This association was destroyed, as a result of a disastrous lockout by the Chicago Northwestern and the 1888 strike against the Chicago, Burlington and Quincy which had equally unfortunate results. Building on what was left of the S.M.A.A., several lodges met in Kansas City in October of 1854 and formed the Switchmen's Union of North America.
By the time of its merger into the United Transportation Union in 1969, the single Chicago labor organization of 1877 had grown to international status with 275 lodges in the United States and Canada having a combined membership of 12,000.
CHRONOLOGY
1877 Switchmen's Mutual Aid Association of North America organized
1886 Switchmen's Association organized
1889 Switchmen's Association affiliated with the Supreme Council of United Orders of Railway Employees
1894 Switchmen's Association dissolved in July
Switchmen's Union of North America organized on October 13
1906 Switchmen's Union of North America affiliated with the American Federation of Labor
1926 Switchmen's Union of North America becomes charter member of the Railway Labor Executives Association
1935 Switchmen's Union of North America affiliated with the Canadian Labor Congress
1969 Switchmen's Union of North America joined with the B.R.T., B.L.F. and E., and O.R.C.B. to form the United Transportation Union
Scope and Contents
One-hundred and thirty-one linear feet of documents comprising the greatest bulk of S.U.N.A. records have been deposited with the Labor Management Docu-mentation Center of the New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations as part of the U.T.U.-Cornell Joint Railway Labor History Project.
Included in this collection are constitutions; by-laws, convention and Board of Director Minutes; officer's records; financial documents; strike, arbitration, wage and vacation files and a host of ancillary documents and photographs as well as oral history transcripts in which S.U.N.A. leaders discuss the merger with the U.T.U. All these items are described in the listing below. The collection, in addition, contains memorabilia including convention badges, union buttons, broadsides, initiation relics and a host of other fascinating artifacts which bring to life the ritual which was so much a part of early union life. These artifacts will be described in a separate listing.
The collection has been divided into several record series, the order of which is outlined in the Table of Contents. At the beginning of each record series,
there is a scope note which explains the content and arrangement of that series and which may offer further information about related data. Series are occasionally further divided into a number of elite-series which are seldom more than topical headings. Finally, there is an alphabetic name and subject index to the entire listing following page 296.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5034 MB: Switchmen's Union of North America Memorabilia 5034 P: Switchmen's Union of North America Photographs 5084: Switchmen's Union of North America Additional Records 5405 mf: Switchmen's Union of North America Constitutions on Microfilm 5406 mf: Switchmen's Union of North America Arbitration on Microfilm 5447: Switchmen's Union of North America Additional Unification Minutes and Convention Proceedings 5556: Switchmen's Union of North America Additional Records 5556 AV: Switchmen's Union of North America Audio-Visual Materials 5590: Switchmen's Union of North America Lake Shore Lodge 55 Membership Registers 5613: Switchmen's Union of North America Oakland Lodge 158 Meeting Minutes 5630: W.B. Meyers Papers
Railroads -- Employees -- Labor unions -- United States -- Sources; Blanchard, Gordon; Brindley, J. P.; Carter, Paul; Cashen, Thomas Cecil, 1879-1959.; Chisholm, L. C.; Clark, George; Collins, Daniel; Demond, Joseph; Doty, Fred; Elliot, P.; Fallon, James; Ferguson, Clarence; Fleete, William A.; Globen, A. J.; Glover, A. J.; Godfrey, R.; Green, William, 1872-1952; Hawley, F. T.; Heberling, Samuel E.; Inglis, F.; Klatte, William; Lightfoot, Charles; McDaniels, C. E.; Mitchell, George; Mooney, Thomas J., 1882-1942; Moore, Tom; Morton, Eugene; Neehan, N. S.; Perry, John M.; Rook, David; Scillian, Raymond; Speirs, Neil P.; Stapp, James; Tamaska, J.; Van Heck, J.; Watson, Harry, 1876-1930; Weir, Robert; Welch, M. R.; Ann Arbor Railroad Company; Atlantic Coast Line Railroad Company; Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers (U.S.); Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen; Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen; Chicago & Eastern Illinois Railroad Company; Chicago Great Western Railway Company (1940-1968); Chicago, Rock Island, and Pacific Railroad Company (1866-1880); Conference on Progressive Political Action; Denver and Rio Grande Western Railroad Company; Eastern Carriers' Conference Committee; Erie Railroad Company; Erie-Lackawanna Railroad Company; Great Northern Railway Company (U.S.); Great Western Railway Company (Canada); Monongahela Railway Company; New York Central Railroad Company; Order of Railway Conductors and Brakemen; Pennsylvania Railroad; Seaboard Air Line Railroad; Southeastern Carriers' Conference Committee; Southern Carriers' Conference Committee; Switchmen's Mutual Aid Association of the United States of America; Switchmen's Union of North America; Switchmen's Union of North America. Ladies' Auxiliary; Texas & Pacific Railway; Trades and Labor Congress of Canada; United Railroad Operating Crafts; United States. National Board of Railroad Wages and Working Conditions; United States. National Mediation Board; United States. National Railroad Adjustment Board; United Transportation Union; Western Carriers' Conference Committee; Wisconsin Central Railroad Company (1871-1899)
3338456
- Constitutions and By-Laws, 1900-1967 and Convention Proceedings, 1895-1927 (Box 1)
  - Switchmen's Union of North America constitutions, by-laws, 1900-1921 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Booklets
  - Constitutions, by-laws: minutes, working papers, 1924-1941 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Bound volume: booklets, manuscript
  - Constitutions, by-laws: Proposed amendments and correspondence of constitution committee, 1947-1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Booklets: Proposed amendments 1947, 1955, 1959, 1963, 1967
  - Constitutions, by-laws: Amendments section 2, 3, 34, 10f, 17-1, 29f, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Manuscript
  - Constitutions, by-laws: Outline for constitution, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Manuscripts
  - Constitutions, by-laws: Mock-up of constitution (Box 1, Folder 6)
    A-H. Manuscript, no date
  - Constitutions, by-laws: Re-typed constitutions and by-laws, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    A-1 - D-1. Manuscript
  - Constitutions, by-laws: Mock-up of constitution (Box 1, Folder 8)
    A-2 - C-2. Manuscript, no date
  - Convention Proceedings, 1895-1921 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Bound volume, manuscript; 1895, 1921
  - Convention proceedings, 1911 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    bound volume, booklet
  - Convention proceedings: Volumes 1, 11, 1927 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Bound volume, manuscript
- Convention Proceedings, 1913-1967 (Box 2)
  - Convention proceedings: Volume 1, 2, 1930 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    bound volume
  - Convention proceedings, 1933 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Convention proceedings, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Bound manuscript
  - Convention proceedings, 1941-1967 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Booklet
  - Convention proceedings: Various convention committee reports, 1933-1947 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Convention proceedings: Various convention committee reports, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    3a. Manuscript
  - Convention proceedings: Resolutions, 1913-1947 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Convention proceedings: Papers regarding the special convention rules committee, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    A-C. Manuscript.
  - Convention proceedings: working papers, 1953 Special Convention (Box 2, Folder 9)
    A-B. Manuscript
  - Convention Proceedings: Working Papers, 1953 Special Convention (Box 2, Folder 10)
    A-2 - B-2. Manuscript.
  - Convention Proceedings: Working paper, correspondence for the conventions, 1941-1951 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    A-3 - C-3. Manuscript.
- Convention Proceedings, 1955-1967 (Box 3)
  - Convention proceedings: Working papers (Delegates, speakers, forms, etc.), 1955 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Convention Proceedings: Constitution Committee, 1955 convention (Box 3, Folder 2)
    A-1 - B-1. Manuscript.
  - Convention proceedings: Convention records, 1955 convention (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Includes: appeals, rules, resolutions, salary, strikes, proposed amendments. Manuscript.
  - Convention proceedings: working papers, 1959 convention (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Convention proceedings: Working papers of various committees, 1959 convention (Box 3, Folder 5)
    A-B. Includes: rules, resolutions, constitution, salary, appeals, credentials, transportation, officers report. Manuscript.
  - Convention proceedings: Working papers for published proceedings, 1963 convention (Box 3, Folder 6)
    A-E. Manuscript.
  - Convention proceedings: Working papers of various committees, 1963 convention (Box 3, Folder 7)
    A-C. Includes: resolution and ritual, rules, transportation and entertainment, credentials, finance and salary, appeals, constitution, officers report, miscellaneous committees. Manuscript.
  - Convention proceedings: Working papers for published proceedings, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    A-2 - C-2. Manuscript.
  - Convention proceedings: Miscellaneous correspondence, resolutions, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Convention proceedings: Rules and reports, 1967 convention (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Manuscript.
  - Convention proceedings: Ballots - Vice President; 1967 Convention (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Convention proceedings: Ballots - 7 man unification; 1967 Convention (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Convention proceedings: Ballots - Board of Directors; 1967 Convention (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Board of Directors Minutes, 1915-1919 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    140-6. Bound manuscript.
- Board of Directors Minutes, Circulars, and Miscellaneous Materials 1915-1968. (Box 4)
  - Grand Board of Directors Minutes, 1920-1926 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Grand Board of Directors Minutes, 1926-1929 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Bound Manuscript
  - Grand Board of Directors Minutes and Minutes of Joint Meeting of Officers, 1920-1947 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Bound manuscript. Minutes: 1920-1930. Minutes of Joint Meeting of Officers: June 7, 1947.
  - Grand Board of Directors Minutes, 1930-1932 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Bound Manuscript. 1931 Minutes - Special
  - Board of Directors Minutes, 1932-1935 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Minutes at Palmer House July 8, 1933; Minutes of Special Meeting October 1, 1933; Minutes with Joint Sub Committee March 14, 1934. Bound manuscript.
  - Board of Directors Minutes, 1936-1938 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Bound manuscript.
  - Board of Directors Minutes: Special sessions, 1931-1938 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Board of Directors Minutes: Minutes, Special Session, 1938-1940 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    Special - May 6, 1940. Bound Manuscript.
  - Board of Directors Minutes, 1942-1944 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Board of Directors Minutes of Regular and Special Sessions, 1945-1948 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Board of Directors Minutes, 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Board of Directors Minutes, 1953-1959 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Board of Directors Minutes, 1959-1961 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Board of Directors Minutes, 1962-1968 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    Manuscript. 1962-1966, 1968
  - Duplicate Material (Box 4, Folder 15)
    Excluded from original finding aid
  - Duplicate Material (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Duplicate Material (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Board of Directors: Circulars (Balance Sheets), 1909-1951 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Board of Directors: Miscellaneous material (Box 4, Folder 19)
    Manuscript, no date.
- Officers Reports 1913-1967 and Correspondence (Blanchard, G.-Cashen, T.C.) (Box 5)
  - Officer Reports, 1913-1927 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Officers Reports, 1930-1951 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Officers Reports: Report of President, 1963-1967 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Booklets. 1963, 1967
  - Officers reports: report of President and Secretary and Treasurer, 1955-1959 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Officers Reports: Reports of Vice President, Board of Directors, Finance and Insurance Board, 1955-1967 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Booklet. 1955, 1959, 1963, 1967.
  - Officers Reports: Report of Secretary and Treasurer, 1963-1967 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Officers Reports: Report of President T.C. Cashen, A.J. Glover, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Officers Reports: Expenses of President N. Spiers, 1959-1967 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Officers Reports: Expenses of Vice President G. Clark, 1955-1967 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Officers Reports: Expenses of various officers, 1910-1967 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Officers Reports: Report of Committee on Officers Reports, 1930-1967 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Manuscript. 1930, 1937, 1957, 1963, 1967.
  - Officers Reports: Report of Ladies' Auxiliary, Instruction to Treasurer form, 1910-1959 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Pamphlets. 1959, 1910.
  - Correspondence - Blanchard G., Vice President of the International, 1953-1955 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    A-C. Manuscript
  - Correspondence: Brindley, J.P., Vice President of the International, 1952-1951 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    Manuscript. 1942, 1951
  - Correspondence: Carter, P., Secretary of the International Board of Directors, 1933-1946 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: Cashen, T.C., President of the International, 1915-1936 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    A-2 - E-2. Manuscript.
- Correspondence (Cashen, T.C.-Ferguson, C.) (Box 6)
  - Correspondence: Cashen, T.C., President of the International, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    A-D. Manuscript.
  - Correspondence: Cashen, T.C., President of the International, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Cashen, T.C., President of the International, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Cashen, T.C., President of the International, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    A-B.
  - Correspondence: Cashen, T.C., President of the International, 1943-1945 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    A-2 - B-2. Manuscript
  - Correspondence: Cashen, T.C., President of the International, 1946-1947 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Chrisholm, L.C., Chairman of the Board of Directors of the International, 1959-1968 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Clark, G., Vice President of the International, 1953-1955 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Clark, G., Vice President of the International., 1956-1959 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Collins, D., Secretary and Treasurer of the International, 1953-1968 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    A-3 - E-3. Manuscript.
  - Correspondence: Demond, J., Vice President of the International, 1953-1955 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Doty, F., Chairman of the Board of Directors of the International, 1955-1962 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: Elliott, P., Vice President of the International, 1953-1955 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: Fallon, James, Vice President of the International, 1954-1960 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: Ferguson, C., Secretary of the International - Personal Financial Records, 1929-1931 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    Bound volume. Manuscript.
  - Correspondence: Ferguson, C., Secretary of the International., 1932-1953 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    A-C. Manuscript. 1932, 1941-1953.
  - Correspondence: Ferguson, C., Secretary of the International, 1954-1957 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Correspondence (Ferguson, C.-Morton, E.) (Box 7)
  - Correspondence: Ferguson, C., Secretary of the International, 1957-1962 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    A-B. Manuscript.
  - Correspondence: Ferguson, C., Secretary of the International, 1963-1969 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Fleete, W., President of the International, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    A-1 - C-1. Manuscript.
  - Correspondence: Fleete, W., President of the International., 1954 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Fleete, W., President of the International, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    A-3 - D-3. Manuscript.
  - Correspondence: Fleete, W., President of the International., 1956 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    A-4 - B-4. Manuscript.
  - Correspondence: Fleete, W., President of the International, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Glover, A.J., President of the International, 1942-1949 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Glover, A.J., President of the International, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Glover, A.J., President of the International, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    A-1 - B-1.
  - Correspondence: Glover, A.J., President of the International, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Glover, A.J., President of the International, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: Godfrey, R., Secretary Pro Tem of the International, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: Hale, N., Chairman of the Board of Directors of the International., 1947-1951 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: Hawley, F., President of the International., 1901-1910 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: Heberling, S.E., President of the International, 1910-1920 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    Manuscript. 1910-1917, 1920.
  - Correspondence: Inglis, F., Vice President of the International, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence: Klatte, W., President of the International, 1948-1958 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence: Lightfoot, C., Vice President of the International, 1934 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence: McDaniels, C.E., President of the International, 1953-1959 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence: Mitchell, G., Member of the Board of Directors of the International, 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence: Moore, T.F., Secretary of the Board of Directors of the International, 1957-1968 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    Manuscript. 1957, 1968.
  - Correspondence, Morton E., Vice President of the International, 1941-1952 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Correspondence (Neehan, N.S.-Wingate, L.E.) and Financial Records 1951-1957. (Box 8)
  - Correspondence: Neehan, N.S., Secretary of the Board of Directors of the International, 1926-1942 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Manuscript. 1926-1927, 1932, 1942
  - Correspondence: Perry, J., Secretary and Treasurer of the Board of Directors of the International, 1933-1958 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Poland, C., Vice President of the International, 1947-1953 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Porter, L., Secretary of the Board of Directors of the International, 1933-1935 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Rook, D., editor of "Switchmen's", 1945-1952 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Sicilian, N., Secretary of the Board of Directors of the International, 1947-1951 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    5a. Manuscript.
  - Correspondence: Speirs, N., Vice President of the International, 1944-1955 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    Manuscript. 1944, 1952-1955.
  - Correspondence: Speirs, N., Vice President of the International, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    A-2 - B02. Manuscript.
  - Correspondence: Speirs, N., Vice President of the International, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    A-3 - B-3. Manuscript
  - Correspondence: Speirs, N., Vice President of the International, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Speirs, N., Vice President of the International, 1959-1961 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Speirs, N., Vice President of the International, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: Speirs, N., Vice President of the International, 1963-1968 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    A-1 - C-1. Manuscript
  - Correspondence: Stapp, J., Vice President of the International, 1956-1962 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    Manuscript. 1956-1958, 1962.
  - Correspondence: Tamaki, J., Vice President of the International, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: Van Heck, J., Vice President of the International, 1947-1965 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    4a. Manuscript. 1947, 1951, 1965.
  - Correspondence: Watson, H., Vice President of the International, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence: Weir, R., Secretary to the Board of Directors of the International, 1936-1939 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence: Weir, R., Secretary to the Board of Directors of the International, 1940-1951 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    A-3 - B-3. Manuscript.
  - Correspondence: Welch, M., Secretary and Treasurer of the International., 1918-1925 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    Manuscript. 1918, 1925.
  - Correspondence: Wingate, L.E., Secretary to the Grand Board of Directors of the International, 1929 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Financial Records: Annual Audit, 1951-1952 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Financial Records: Annual Audit, 1952-1953 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Financial Records: Annual Audit., 1953-1954 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Financial Records: Annual Audit, 1954-1955 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Financial Records: Annual Audit, 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Financial Records: Annual Audit, 1956-1957 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    A-3 - C-3. Manuscript
- Financial Records 1951-1968 and Officers' Files (Carter, Paul-Cashen, T.C.) (Box 9)
  - Financial Records: Annual Audit, 1957-1958 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Financial Records: Annual Audit, 1958-1959 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Financial Records: Annual Audit., 1959-1960 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Financial Records: Annual Audit, 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Financial Records: Annual Audit, 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Financial Records: Annual audit, 1962-1963 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Financial Records: Annual Audit, 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    A-3 - B-2. Manuscript.
  - Financial Records: Annual Audit, 1964-1965 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Financial Records: Annual Audit., 1965-1966 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Financial Records: Annual Audit, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Financial Records: 8 month audit, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Financial Records: Annual Audit, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Financial Records: Minutes of Finance and Insurance Board, 1951-1953 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    Manuscript. 1951-1953 (not complete)
  - Financial Records, 1951-1958 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    Bound Manuscript.
  - Financial Records, 1959-1963 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Financial Records: Miscellaneous working papers, 1951-1961 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Carter, Paul: Miscellaneous Records, 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Manuscript Correspondence.
  - Casen, T.C.: Miscellaneous Records, 1925-1947 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Manuscript Correspondence. 1925-1926, 1942, 1947.
- Officers' Files (Collins, D.) (Box 10)
  - Collins, D.: Employees' Exhibit Number 1, 6A-B, 13-15, 22-25, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Collins, D.: Employees' Exhibit Numbers 26-29, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 2)